He probably would have been craving if it wasn't because he had given it to write a novel.
During high school things had always come in between.
After the student, he had thought.
Then it's time.
It would be easily autobiographical and sharp.
Shake the old one, wrap all the old cobwebs and crap.
He saw in front of him with a room with floor -to -ceiling and a desk under a large window.
On the desk there was a typewriter and piles of paper,
and reverse a spinning chair, in black polo shirt and
with growth hair and a cigarette glowing between point and middle finger
Sit Martin Berg.
He started with a story about a man and a woman
At a hotel in Pamplona, vaguely inspired by Wallace.
There was an atmosphere of imminent threats in the hotel room that is quite satisfied with,
In that short story he had
got to a kind of chaotic feeling that was quite successful,
And it had also been printed in the school newspaper.
But it was a short story,
And what was a short story other than a strength test for the inevitable novel.
He had not pondered any intrigue, because he thought it all
would resolve in the meantime.
And by the way, the intrigue was not the important thing.
The important thing was,
Yes, what was the important thing really?
What did William Wallace really write about?
Everything that happened in the stories did not seem very important.
That was not what they hung on.
He thought that the intrigue had to be arranged then and wrote what fell him in,
Which mostly consisted of escapades with Gustav during the fall and spring.
Martin had provided yourself with the cover name Johan but did not come up with anything that really suited Gustav,
So far he got hot G.
Johan and G drove around, went to a museum, ignored the student party and
instead climbed some height, where they sat in the grass
While the sun went down and had philosophical conversation about the meaning of life that extended over several pages.
The phone rang, with Martin just had to write a little more about how G snatched snuff on the attendance set
so that they had to
just run off hell
And how they had taken back on the slope below the Kungsladugårdsskolan,
And how Johan sniffs the first time.
Which was fun for five minutes
Before it took its end in a magnificent spya that got some aunts and glow in a general disapproval.
When he didn't know how to continue, he browsed any of Wallace novels
To see how he had done.
In Patagonia days there was a piece that gave him scams.
The book's main character, the young Bill, had just come to Paris.
He was as determined to succeed as he was hungry, alone and recently rejected.
Bill pulled around on the streets in what Wallace called "the ink malaria fever"
And longed for the desk in the hotel room as much as he feared it.
And this is how Martin reads then in
William Wallace Book.
"Given how demanding the author's profession is, it may seem strange that it exerts a
Such attraction to young souls.
No one, not even Bill Bradley,
could fully and firmly imagine ever -inspired at the desk,
pouring out of sources as never -sitting, possessed, feverish, driven forward by forces he did not understand
and could not control.
No, there was an ever -present doubt.
If I fall now I am lost.
Few professions attract happiness seekers with such headings:
It is well gold digging and writing.
Yet they are looking for themselves.
They sit down at a table with paper and pen.
They are looking within themselves for the first sentence,
The spider -thin fishing line they are going to testify.
They understand how long it will take, what work is in front of them, but still they continue.
And why?
To write,
It is to conquer the world.
To make it his and herself to God.
In writing you get free access to all rooms, to hearts and souls, and the most sacred;
The unknown is laid for one's feet.
You get a chance at eternity.
To write is to refuse die. ”
Early when I started writing this, I was determined that it would take place Gothenburg.
A lot because I lived here,
but also because I felt that
There was also not really a good and great Gothenburg depiction.
A writer that I had read a lot of,
And likes a lot, is Hjalmar Söderberg.
lies there and vibrates between
the unknown and the known between one's self
and the larger world
and that it is at the same time may be some kind of return
And thus also very comforting to read.
At the same time as there is also a kind of discovery journey into something new and unknown.
What it is that makes those as readers be able to get to that kind of creative process,
As you are, a kind of co -creation
Where you make your own book.
There are some works that have read about since the late teens,
Hjalmar Söderberg among other things,
And often I find myself returning to a whole new novel.
I naturally recognize the intrigue and story even though I have often forgotten
how it ends and so
But depending on where I found myself in life and what entrance I had in the reading
So I think I can discover something new there.
Maybe there is something that can happen with all books, I actually don't know but
I believe, I some kind of feeling that
this kind of novel that is quite
that depicts development not only
Write something
Like a human being
can one use to make your own story
and do something creative with self
that may be something completely different from that as
I intended to lie there in
or as I myself have thought that I want to try to achieve
Then I'm happy.
If it can get
Brand new novels that arise
with each reading.